In an era in which the nations of
the world were waging a fierce war
of information just out of sight,
in order to keep an eye on one of the
key players of the Ostanian government,
Westalis put Operation Strix into motion.
The extremely skilled agent
conducting this mission,
Agent Twilight, had completed Phase 1:
creating a pretend family and getting his
daughter into a prestigious school.
Currently, his daughter has
successfully obtained one Stella
out of the eight necessary to
become an Imperial Scholar,
and the mission has moved into Phase 2,
attending the social gathering that
his target, Desmond, will attend.
Well, apparently I've discovered that
I can take these yawn-filled days
And turn them into movies
I've found the secret and trick to it
Under this sky where we don't get along
I closed my heart and locked it
That's how I've managed to live my life
And the melodies now overlap
I wanted a sign, no matter how small
That I could actually find
better than any streetlight
I put a ribbon on each of the
sights that my eyes pick out
And I collect them like souvenirs
as I continue down this path home
The seasons each say hello,
and I shed a few tears as I go
Where should I begin to talk about
this way home that you've given me?
I walk and walk and sometimes
rush on my way to see you
I run and run, wait, no, I should
still walk on my way to see you
INVESTIGATE THE GENERAL HOSPITAL
Your next social studies
assignment will be to
research an occupation that
you are interested in.
You may visit your parents' places of work
or go interview local shops or companies.
You may even interview famous people
through your parents' connections.
Of course, if you'd like to know more about
educators, you may interview me, as well.
I will gladly tell you about
our hallowed profession.
Compile your findings in a report.
You will be presenting it on Friday.
Will you be interviewing
your father, Lord Damian?
If I can talk to him.
I guess I'll just make it
quick and ask my dad.
What about you, Anya?
A job investigation?
I was told to ask why you chose your
job or how I can get into that job.
And I'm supposed to watch
you do your job, too.
Huh? My job?
Wh-What should I tell her? My profession?
Which one?
Please listen carefully, Miss Anya.
I will now show you the
ways of my profession.
Okee.
At first, I started this job so that
I could take care of my brother,
but now, I'm very proud of it.
Even the Shopkeeper was saying that this
profession was similar to being in the army,
and it is very important because
we lay down our lives for our country.
Oh, the Shopkeeper is
calling with my next job.
So this person must be my client.
He is truly a traitorous pig!
It seems he's done many horrific things
that I couldn't possibly tell you about.
Well, let's start this observation.
Can you keep up, Miss Anya?
Yep.
The Shop will let me know how many enemies
there are and how the security is laid out,
so all I have to do is get inside.
I will usually kill any enemy on sight,
but I must not ever kill the wrong person,
so studying the briefing
documents carefully is a must.
There's nothing shameful about
this work, so I can be confident.
An intruder!
I think what makes this job worthwhile
is that I truly feel like I'm cleaning
up the filth in this country.
When I think about all the lives
that are being protected by my job,
I feel extra strength
flowing into every strike.
What's essential in this job is honing my
body and my techniques to their limit.
Also, it's important to study human anatomy.
Since I'm dealing with other humans,
the least I can do is put them out of
their misery as painlessly as possible.
I do beg your pardon,
but I will be taking your life.
For example, if you ■■■■■
the ■■■■■ of someone's neck,
they will die rather quickly.
You could also precisely attack one's
vital points like their brain or heart.
Are you all right, Miss Anya?!
Let's just tell Loid that we
went to the tomato festival!
I think I'm going to investigate Papa's job.
I-I see... That's probably for the best.
Working at city hall is a fine job,
but it might be rather boring.
I'm home.
Papa! Blah, blah, yadda, yadda.
Hm? All right, then.
Days
Later,
at
Berlint
General
Hospital
The psychiatry department at
this hospital is my workplace.
I've told them in advance that you're
coming, but don't trouble anyone, all right?
Yep.
It's huge.
This is the longest-established
hospital in the capital.
It probably would've been easier to
fake being a general practitioner,
but many prominent names from the political
and business world frequent this hospital.
This lets me infiltrate their social circles
and steal plenty of information.
I haven't said anything you'd
need to take notes about yet.
By the way, why are you dressed like that?
This is classic investigation fashion.
I see.
Most psychiatrists don't wear lab coats,
but this probably makes
me look the part more.
So, what are you investigating?
First, why did you choose this job?
Why I chose this job?
Well, let's see...
Everyone gets a cold sometimes, right?
But it's not just the body.
The mind can go through that, too.
There are a lot of people who
catch colds, but in their minds.
But Second Son told me I wouldn't
catch a cold because I'm stupid.
I see... Well, keep getting along with him.
But anyway, I wanted to
help people like that.
There are still lots of veterans who are still
suffering even years after the war ended.
Since Desmond is such a recluse,
I figured that if I'm lucky,
being a doctor might give me a chance
to approach him if he ever got sick.
I made up my mind when I was in college.
Um, the next question is, "What's the
atomsphere like at your workplace?"
You mean "atmosphere."
Oh, Dr. Forger.
Is this your daughter?
These are my colleagues. Say hello.
It is a pweasure to meet
your acquiantenance.
She's so cute!
You're doing your homework?
What a good little girl!
Oh, her eyes are so big!
She looks like a princess.
Have some snacks.
"Papa's workplace is paradise."
Good for you.
What is Papa like at work?
Oh, he does everything with such style.
He's so careful and kind
with the patients, too.
Your father's amazing, young lady.
He became an important part of our
team as soon as he transferred in.
But despite that, he's so down to
earth and respected by everyone.
By the way, my neurologist friend was hoping
you'd come to our next meeting, Dr. Forger.
The director also wanted
you to come golfing.
Papa is popular?
Well... I make sure to be sociable.
Okay, I'll talk to the director...
It's always good to spread
out my connections.
It makes it easier to obtain
intel and more connections,
and most importantly for a spy, it makes
people think, "What? No way he's a spy!"
It's crucial to completely embody how
I want people to view this individual.
I need to try not to stand out
too much, but remain sociable.
"What? No way..."
Why in the world do you keep taking
notes at the most random times?
"What is hard about this job?"
That's a great question, young lady.
Let's see...
I'd say it's the fact that we deal with
people's hearts, which we can't see.
Doctors aren't wizards, after all.
We can't read other people's minds.
Heh.
Why do you look so smug?
Because we can't read minds, we have
to throw away our preconceptions,
and observe them assiduously and carefully.
Just like a spy dealing with their target.
The most important thing is to
build trust with your patient.
The biggest difference
would be the fact that
in the end, spies betray that trust, and...
Everything is very delicate
and involves risks, so...
Mm, snacks. Yum, yum.
Ooh, would you like some more?
Want some juice?
Want to take a psychological test?
Never mind. I'm not answering any more.
Papa, you're so serious.
But that's what makes him so great.
We're hoping he continues to hone his skills
so he can open his own clinic someday.
My apologies, but I've just
been so busy with my research.
I guess the hardest part is dealing
with my mission and my side job.
Well, we should get back to work.
Bye now, Anya!
I want to actually see you in action.
You want to see a consultation?
I can't allow that.
It violates the patient's privacy.
I can't show much of my
research to outsiders, either.
I guess I can at least show
you the consultation room.
I don't plan on using
this room today anyway.
It's different from the operatering room.
It looks like a normal room.
We try to make sure our
patients don't feel anxious.
Where's the brain modification machine?
What exactly do you think I practice here?
Enough of that nonsense.
Let's finish the other questions.
Seriously, what cartoon did you get that from?
Anya's done now. Also bored now.
Hey! Don't go touching
things without permission!
If you fuss too much, I'm going to get mad.
There's a secret escape passage
behind this bookshelf just in case there's
an emergency related to the mission.
It'll open up if you turn the lever.
Secret passage! Lever!
Must be a WISE agent.
Sorry, something came up.
If you're done with your assignment,
should we have Yor come pick you up?
I will wait until you're
done with work, Papa.
Being a spy is rough.
All right. In that case, you can
keep yourself busy with this.
We use this in our practice.
We have our patients place these toys
and props the way they want in these boxes.
It's really fun.
That seems boring.
Just a reminder, do not touch anything else.
Yep.
I'll be back in about ten minutes.
Heh.
We should be getting documents on
the revised DSM by the weekend.
Thank you.
Of course, to go with the rest of the façade,
a number of my coworkers have
also infiltrated this hospital.
Another separate mission.
What about the adjustments
with my hospital schedule?
Already done.
Was that little girl Anya Forger?
She seems quite attached to you.
She's unpredictable, so she's a real handful.
I'm surprised that she's beyond
what you expected, Doctor.
Ooh!
Exploration is so exciting!
Secret passage is so cramped...
Our discussion today will be on
psychic phenomena and neuroscience.
A serious meeting?
Around 5% of the cases reported
have no explanation—
Hmph, nonsense.
Anyone who goes on about ghosts and
such just suffers from mythomania.
Or they could be illusions
caused by brain dysfunction.
This is all clearly unscientific.
They're talking about ghosts? So exciting!
Did you hear something?
Er, there's no room above us, though.
Oh, no! They'll find the secret passage!
I-I'm sure it's just your imagination.
Anyway, as for treatment
in these situations,
we should take a careful approach—
There's no point in debating
this. Let's end this meeting.
I have to get back. Papa will return soon.
My leg is stuck and I can't get it out!
Anya's in big trouble!
What the?! There's something there!
Is that a baby crying?!
It's a ghost! It has to be a ghost!
I got it out! I have to hurry back!
It's gone?
It's true!
The rumors about a ghost of a baby
who died due to medical
malpractice were true!
G-Gentlemen, let us continue this meeting.
Indeed!
From now on, let us take patients
who speak of ghosts seriously!
Whew...
Now, then... I wonder
how her box turned out.
Papa's back!
I have to hurry up and make something.
I'm back.
P-Playing with dolls is so much fun.
Let's have a look.
You see, this gives us some insight into
the deeper parts of a patient's psyche.
It looks like your mind is full of...
utter chaos!
Wh-What in the world is this?
I've never seen anything like this before!
I just dumped everything in.
Wh-Why are there so many
scattered and half-buried dolls?
They, um... They were all defeated by
the bad guy's Rolling Sweep Attack.
Unbelievable. I don't know what to make
of this, but it's clearly a disaster!
I couldn't even see the signs
because I've been so busy.
She was dragged out of the orphanage
by an adult she didn't know.
Of course she would be
under a lot of stress.
Er, Papa, this is just...
I'm sure she did the best any child
could do to endure it all.
But to think the darkness within
her heart had grown so much...
No, maybe I just pretended not to notice it.
Yes, this is a result of my own weakness.
I'm a failure as a spy.
I must do something immediately!
Why don't we go home for the day?
Let's stop by a bookstore to get
you the new volume of Spy Wars.
Y-Yay...
After dinner, why don't we
put your report together?
Did you take some good notes?
Papa, that's—
He'll see the spy stuff!
This is—
I can't read any of this!
This is, uh... yes.
Anya will do her best to
make the report herself.
I see. Well, good girl. You're the best!
Mama, we're home.
Welcome home.
Did you get to see Loid's amazing
concussive recovery method at work?
Concussive?
Er, uh, Yor... That's just
for extreme emergencies—
He punched and kicked his
patients with such might!
It was fantastic to witness!
Papa's filled with violence.
Borf.
Yor!
I realized that I also wanted
to carry on in this profession.
The end.
An elegant report that
conveyed your feelings well.
Next, Anya Forger.
Papa is a sp—spechulist in
mental health. A very good one.
Papa works very hard
every day by not sleeping
or taking stomach medicine so that his
patients can have some peace of cake.
He even said he wants to help people
who had troubles during war times.
Oh, how wonderful.
Good show, Loid Forger.
In order to build trust with his targets,
he talks to them assisisisiduly and carefully.
Targets?
Papa is very desperate to make conneshuns.
He golfs at his workplace
and creates shady channels.
Oh, and they give you snacks there.
Snacks?! Is that a codeword for bribes?!
Oh, and he apparently hits his
patients every once in a while.
Loid Forger?!
What's the matter, Twilight?
Er, I just got a very bad feeling.
Loid was summoned to the
school a few days later,
but he managed to smooth everything
over with his superb eloquence.
It says "top secret." Must be
another top-secret mission.
It's a code.
SECRET CODE
Saturday, 0800, come to the bridge.
DECIPHER THE PERPLEXING CODE
Well, you're definitely as elite as they say
you are if you could decipher that code.
Anya's going to make a code, too!
And there she goes playing spy again.
Anya...
Top secret!
No one's going to be able to read that,
let alone crack the code.
Her handwriting is impossible to read,
even with my superb decoding skills.
Shock!
I need to go in for my night shift.
Make sure you study.
It smells so nice and clean now.
Mama, I have a request, please.
What is it, Miss Anya?
Could you write something
for me just like I ask?
SECRET CODE
The code is complete.
Listen well. This is a top-secret mission.
Tell no one.
Borf.
I've got some mail for you.
Miss?
You need to put stamps on letters
and put them in the mailbox, okay?
Shock! He rejected the code!
You mustn't do that, Miss Anya.
Oh, what's this?
What strange text. Is it some kind of prank?
Come to think of it, my son
wrote something similar.
He was copying some cartoon
called Spy something.
Oh, I see.
I guess that little girl is
always pretending to be a spy.
Heya. What're you doing there?
Scruffyhead.
Is Loid around?
Man, so he's not home? Oh, well.
I guess I'll come by again later.
What's this? A message from Loid?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
It's top secret.
Good morning, Anya.
Huh? What's this? A letter?
It's not?
Oh, I know! It's that quiz that
everyone's raving about lately.
It's top secret.
Jeez... Anya, you meanie.
Just tell me the answer already!
Top secret!
Huh? What the heck is this?
Heh. It's a secret code.
Just try and crack it.
Why the heck do I have to crack this?!
Crack it yourself!
Anya's excited to see who shows up tomorrow.
Heh. Well done.
You actually cracked the code.
Oh, this is the thing from yesterday.
I can see that it's some kind
of code, but what the hell is it?
This is nice handwriting...
Could it be from a woman?
It does smell nice, like soap.
Could this be a love letter?!
Could you give this to him for me?
Don't tell anyone, okay?
This is a top-secret romance.
"Saturday, 0800, come to the bridge."
Don't you dare try and underestimate the
best informant in the East and the West!
Cracking a code or two is easy as pie!
Though I couldn't sleep a wink
because I was so excited!
Man, that sun's bright!
To think she'd call me
out here using a code.
I wonder where this agent works.
Or wait, she could just be
obsessed with mysteries!
Like, "Crack the code of love
and come see me"?!
Top secret...
NIGHTFALL
FIRST FIT OF JEALOUSY